automobilemove.com 2016-02-07

# Automobile Move - Auto Transport Services

Call for the most accurate quote

### Get Sipping Quote in 3 simple steps

##### Please tell us about the vehicle you want to ship.

* * *

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Transport, Inc website. On some pages, you can contact us via a fill-out form, request a Transport quotation or place a Transport order. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number 

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you request a Transport quotation or place a Transport order, you may submit an alternate contact name for pick-up and drop-off information. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

Name   
Phone Number  

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing a Transport order, requesting a Transport quotation or requesting information about our company only to respond to your request. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to fullfill your request. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing a Transport order only to complete your Transport order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive and to communicate with you about your Transport order. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website. For example, we may collect information that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals, nor do we share this information with outside parties.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by sending your request to Transport. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at or send us an email at info@stateautoTransport.com.

* * *
